holidaytravel.co 2016-04-03

# Privacy Policy of Holidaytravel.co - Holiday Travel

**What information we collect and how** The information we collect via the Website may include:

  * Any personal details you knowingly provide us with through forms and our email, such as name, address, telephone number etc.
  * Your IP Address, this is a string of numbers unique to your computer that is recorded by our web server when you request any page or component on the Website. This information is used to monitor your usage of the Website.
  * Data recorded by the Website which allows us to recognise you and your preferred settings, this saves you from re-entering information on return visits to the site. Such data is recorded locally on your computer through the use of cookies. Most browsers can be programmed to reject, or warn you before downloading cookies, information regarding this may be found in your browsers 'help' facility.

**What we do with the information**  
Any personal information we collect from this website will be used in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and other applicable laws. The details we collect will be used:

  * To provide pre and after sales service. We may pass your details to a third-party organisation to supply services you have requested and/or to provide pre and after-sales service. These third-parties are obliged to keep your details securely;
  * In certain cases we may use your email address to send you information of other services provided by us. In such a case you will be offered the option to opt out of future communications.

We may need to pass the information we collect to other companies for administrative purposes. We may use third parties to carry out certain activities, such as processing and sorting data, monitoring how customers use the Website and issuing our e-mails for us. Third parties will NOT be allowed to use your personal information for their own purposes.

**Other Websites**

This privacy policy only covers this website. Any other websites which may be linked to by our website are subject to their own policy, which may differ from ours

===================================

=========================

use third parties to carry out certain activities, such as processing and sorting data, monitoring how customers use the Website and issuing our e-mails for us. Third parties will NOT be allowed to use your personal information for their own purposes.

**Other Websites**

This privacy policy only covers this website. Any other websites which may be linked to by our website are subject to their own policy, which may differ from ours

use third parties to carry out certain activities, such as processing and sorting data, monitoring how customers use the Website and issuing our e-mails for us. Third parties will NOT be allowed to use your personal information for their own purposes.

**Other Websites**

This privacy policy only covers this website. Any other websites which may be linked to by our website are subject to their own policy, which may differ from ours

**Other Websites**

This privacy policy only covers this website. Any other websites which may be linked to by our website are subject to their own policy, which may differ from ours
